<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Home</title>
    <link>https://mill2994.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:21:07 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mill2994.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Discord Bot</title>
      <link>https://mill2994.github.io/projects/benbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:21:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mill2994.github.io/projects/benbot/</guid>
      <description>With this project I decided I was going to branch out from the types of projects I have typically worked on. I wanted to create something me and other people would be able to use daily, that would provide utility. BenBot was my answer! BenBot is a discord bot that I created for my server with my friends. I decided to make my own bot so that I could have full control over how it worked, and I would be able to implement the features that I really wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancake or Waffle?</title>
      <link>https://mill2994.github.io/projects/pancakevwaffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:21:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mill2994.github.io/projects/pancakevwaffle/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to learn more about machine learning and fill the gap in my knowledge the best I could, as I never got to take a dedicated class about the topic. This inspired me to create a program that would implement some of the basics of machine learning. I created a tool that labeled whether a picture was of a pancake or a waffle. The program achieves around 90% accuracy for the labeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire Risk Forecasting Tool</title>
      <link>https://mill2994.github.io/projects/capstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 15:21:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mill2994.github.io/projects/capstone/</guid>
      <description>For my computer science capstone course at Michigan State, I worked with the Anthropocene Institute to help create the Wildfire Risk Forecasting Tool. The goal for the project was to create an educational, open source, and easy to access tool for forecasting current and future wildfires. The web app features a plotly map and a form, as well as additional pages to learn more about wildfires. The form contains preset scenarios or adjustable options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
